ebizautos.com 2016-03-16

# Privacy Policy | eBizAutos

**LOOKSLIKE, INC. IS COMMITTED TO YOUR PRIVACY**

LooksLike, Inc. (“Us,” “We,” or “Our”) values Your patronage and respects Your privacy rights. As part of the normal operation of Our services, We collect and, in some cases, may disclose information about You. This Privacy Policy describes, among other things, the types of information collected about You when You visit this website (ebizautos.com) (the “Website”), how Your information may be used and when it may be disclosed, how You can control the use of and disclosure of Your information, and how Your information is protected. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information that You may provide to third parties, for example, other sites linked to Our Website. You should contact such third parties directly to determine their respective privacy policies.

This Privacy Policy is governed by Our Terms of Use, which is incorporated herein by reference. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. For more information, please refer to the paragraph entitled “Changes to this Privacy Policy” detailed below. If You believe We have not adhered to this Privacy Policy or if You have any other questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact Us at [privacy@ebizautos.com](mailto:privacy@ebizautos.com).

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM YOU AND WHY?**

We collect and maintain a variety of Personal Information about You to enable Us to provide You with the best service. “Personal Information” is information about You by which You may be identified. We currently collect Personal Information through email and various online inquiry forms on Our Website. The Personal Information We collect and maintain about You includes:

  * Your name,
  * Your email address,
  * Your phone number, and
  * Your zip code, and
  * Unique identifiers, such as a customer number held in a cookie, an Internet Protocol (IP) address, a processor or device serial number, or other unique identifiers.

We only collect Personal Information that You voluntarily provide to Us.* We also use Your Personal Information for other things that may include, but are not limited to, the following:

**• Contacting You**

We may use Your Personal Information to communicate with You in the event We have any questions with regard to any online inquiry You may have or if, in accordance with Our Terms and Conditions, We need to contact You. We may also contact You to tell You about products and services provided by Our Partners, other affiliates and other third-party organizations.

**• Interactions**

Each time You interact with Our Website, the details of Your interaction are collected and retained by Us.

**• Correspondence**

We intend to retain any correspondence, including facsimiles, mail and emails, sent to Us. We also may retain correspondence such as customer service emails from Us to You. We may delete such records over time.

**WHAT GENERAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM YOU AND WHY?**

“General Information” is information about You or Your activities on Our Website that does not identify You personally. When You use the Internet, Your web browser or software may communicate certain information to the host websites You visit. This information may include the capabilities and features of Your computer, Your mobile device, and Your movement and activity within a particular Site. We use this General Information to generate statistics about visitors to Our Website. The methods used to collect this information may include:

**• Use of Cookies**

Cookies are a standard technology used by commercial web services to store small pieces of information on Your hard drive by sending a small string of text to Your browser. They make Your use of Our Website more pleasing and efficient by “personalizing” Your user interface, for example, or identifying which parts of a site You have previously visited. They also enable Us to pre-populate, or automatically fill out, forms and schedules, or to assist You in visiting multiple pages within Our Website during the same session without having to re-enter Your password multiple times. For Your convenience, We also use longer-lasting cookies to display Your email address on Our sign-in form so that You do not have to retype Your email address each time You log in to Your Account on Our Website. Cookies enable Us to tailor the information You receive and to assist Our Partners by identifying You as having an Account with Us. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, unless You have configured Yours not to accept them. In order for Us to provide You with services on Our Website, Your browser must accept cookies, as they are essential for site administration and security. We do not use cookies either to collect individually identifiable information or to collect non-individually identifiable information using a cookie that is combined with a personal identifier.

**• Web Beacons**

Small graphic images or web programming code called web beacons (also known as “pixel tags” or “clear GIFs”) may be included on the pages of the Website and in email messages We send You. Web beacons or other similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, such as to count visitors to the Website, monitor how You navigate the Website or to count how many particular articles or links posted on the Website were actually viewed.

**• Mobile Device Identifiers**

Certain mobile service providers uniquely identify mobile devices and We may inadvertently capture specific mobile information if You access the Website through a mobile device. Our Website does not require or use geo-specific information from mobile devices, but We do, however, receive device IP Address information that may give a rough location of the device.

**• Embedded Scripts**

An embedded script is programming code designed to collect information about Your use of this Website, such as the links You click on. The code is temporarily downloaded to Your computer from Our web server or a third party provider, is active only while You are connected to the Website and is deactivated or deleted once You leave the Website.

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

The information We collect is used to (i) to respond to Your inquiries; (ii) provide customer services and resolve any complaints; (iii) improve Our Website and to service and resolve any technical problems; (iv) communicate with You concerning the products and services offered on the Website by Us or any of Our Partners; (v) cross-reference with other Personal Information that We have acquired about You or may acquire about You through other sources; (vi) create aggregate data; (vii) ensure compliance with Our Terms of Use; and (viii) comply with any applicable laws and regulations. We may provide Your information to government officials and agencies as required by law, and Partners as part of business operations, transaction processing, and marketing efforts, as identified below. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Partner” shall mean any person or entity with whom We enter into any kind of business transaction who is under an obligation to Us to use reasonable care to keep Personal Information confidential.

**DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, We will not sell, trade, or disclose to third parties any Personal Information obtained by Us through Our Website or from Our Partners about You. If disclosed in accordance with this Privacy Policy, We cannot control, and are not responsible for, the manner in which any of such companies and other entities use Your Personal Information. We may disclose Personal Information (i) that We in good faith believe is necessary or appropriate to cooperate in investigations of fraud, intellectual property infringements or other activity that is illegal or may expose Us or You to legal liability, or to conduct investigations of violations of Our Terms of Use; (ii) when required by law or to comply with a court order, subpoena, search warrant or other legal process; (iii) to comply with legal, regulatory or administrative requirements of governmental authorities  
(including, without limitation, requests from the governmental agency authorities to view Your Personal Information); (iv) to protect and defend Us, Our subsidiaries, affiliates, and Partners and any of their officers, directors, employees, attorneys, agents, contractors and partners, in connection with any legal action, claim or dispute; (v) to prevent imminent physical harm; (vi) to share aggregated statistical or demographic data with Our affiliates,  
Partners or for public relations (this aggregated information is not tied to Personal Information); (vii) to provide data, including Personal Information about You, with Our affiliates, subsidiaries and Partners; (viii) to sell or otherwise provide to third parties in the event of a bankruptcy or liquidation; and (ix) to sell or otherwise provide to third parties in the event of a future merger or acquisition by another company. In the event We merge or are acquired by another company, the successor company will have access to Your Personal Information in order to continue to provide services, but would continue to be bound by this Privacy Policy unless and until it is amended as described in the subsection labeled “Changes to this Privacy Policy” below.

**HOW WE PROTECT INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

At times, We offer secure web pages to collect certain kinds of user information and We store certain kinds of data in encrypted form. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on Our system. Although no computer system is completely secure, We believe the measures implemented on Our Website reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

**HOW LONG WE KEEP USER INFORMATION**

We generally keep user data on Our server or in Our archives for as long as We reasonably need it. We may alter this practice according to changing requirements. For example, We may delete some data if needed to free up storage space. We may keep other data for longer periods if the law requires it. In addition, information posted in a public forum could stay in the public domain indefinitely.

Data management requests are administered in an orderly manner to the extent feasible and within Our direct control. Please note that We have greater control over recently collected data than over archived data. Once data is removed from the system and archived, it may not be feasible to accommodate specific requests. In those cases, Our general data retention policy applies.

**DO NOT TRACK**

Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that users can set in their web browsers, which allows them to opt out of tracking by websites and online services. When a user activates DNT, the browser sends a message requesting that the website or online service not track the user. At the present time, standard DNT technology is not yet finalized and not all browsers support DNT; therefore, We do not recognize DNT signals. Instead, information collection and disclosure practices and the choices that We provides to You will continue to operate as described in this Privacy Policy, whether or not a DNT signal is received. For more information about DNT, see http://donottrack.us/.

**PERSONAL CHOICE IN THE DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

If You do not want Us to share Your Personal Information with Our Partners for marketing purposes, or if You do not want to receive certain communications and offers from Us You can “opt out” of such sharing, communications and offers by contacting Us by email at [privacy@ebizautos.com](mailto:privacy@ebizautos.com) or write Us at:

LooksLike, Inc.

5584 S. Fort Apache Road

Las Vegas, Nevada 89148

If You believe that any Personal Information collected by Us about You is not correct or has changed, please send an email message to [privacy@ebizautos.com](mailto:privacy@ebizautos.com) explaining the correction or change and providing any relevant confirmation or reference number.

**SPECIAL NOTE ABOUT CHILDREN**

Our Website is targeted primarily for use by persons 18 years of age and older. We do not currently market to or create special areas for use by children. Accordingly, We do not knowingly collect age identifying information, nor do We knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 13 years. However, We hereby advise all visitors to Our Website under the age of 13 not to disclose or provide any Personal Information on Our Website. In the event that We discover that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to Us, in accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (please see the Federal Trade Commission’s website at www.ftc.gov for more information about this Act), We will delete the child’s Personal Information from Our files to the extent technologically possible.

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

Residents of the State of California may request and obtain from Us, once a year and free of charge, information about the Personal Information (if any) We have disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If You are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit Your request in writing to:

LooksLike, Inc.

5584 S. Fort Apache Road

Las Vegas, Nevada 89148

For all requests, You must put the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the body of Your request as well as Your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. Please note that We will not accept requests via the telephone, e-mail, or by facsimile, and We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information or postage.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

By using Our Website, You agree to this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change, modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If We modify Our Privacy Policy, We will update the “Effective Date” and such changes will be effective upon posting. If We make material changes to this Privacy Policy, We will notify You by posting a notice on the Website, Your “Control Panel,” or by sending You a notice to the email address We have on file for You. Your continued use of the Website following such material changes requires Your affirmative consent to the changes. Any revised Privacy Policy will only apply prospectively to Personal Information collected or modified after the effective date of the revised policy.

**IF YOU HAVE A PRIVACY QUESTION**

If You have a privacy question about Our Website, please email: Customer Service [privacy@ebizautos.com](mailto:privacy@ebizautos.com)

Or write to:

LooksLike, Inc.

5584 S. Fort Apache Road

Las Vegas, Nevada 89148

* When applicable, We may request that You provide Us with Your credit card number. However, We will only collect this number from You in written form and will not ask You to provide it to Us electronically. Moreover, once You provide Us with Your credit card number, it is kept confidential and securely stored in accord with Our company policies.
